[
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "6242cafad543524f1b19c900",
        "correctAnswer": "A swarm",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A host",
            "A brace",
            "A sedge"
        ],
        "question": "What is the word for a group of bees?",
        "tags": [
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "623b5792fd6c701a92118367",
        "correctAnswer": "Japan",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Vietnam",
            "Russia",
            "France"
        ],
        "question": "In which country would you find the Itsukushima Shinto Shrine?",
        "tags": [
            "tourist_attractions",
            "places",
            "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Film & TV",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbf2",
        "correctAnswer": "\"I feel the need - the need for speed!\"",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Bond. James Bond.\"",
            "\"Tell 'em to go out there with all they got and win just one for the Gipper.\"",
            "\"Louis, I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship.\""
        ],
        "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Top Gun'?",
        "tags": [
            "quotes",
            "film",
            "film_and_tv"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950ae5",
        "correctAnswer": "Monaco",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Liechtenstein",
            "United Kingdom",
            "San Marino"
        ],
        "question": "Which of these countries borders France?",
        "tags": [
            "france",
            "europe",
            "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510d1",
        "correctAnswer": "Heart",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Soul",
            "Blood",
            "Eyes"
        ],
        "question": "What part of the body does carditis affect?",
        "tags": [
            "medicine",
            "words",
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f9507f6",
        "correctAnswer": "Europe",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "South America",
            "Oceania",
            "Asia"
        ],
        "question": "The country of Liechtenstein is on which continent?",
        "tags": [
            "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "623b584afd6c701a921183ad",
        "correctAnswer": "Belgium",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Italy",
            "Bosnia & Herzegovina",
            "Brazil"
        ],
        "question": "In which country would you find the city of Bruges?",
        "tags": [
            "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "62506458e12f6dec240bdfac",
        "correctAnswer": "Lovin' You",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Pass the Dutchie",
            "In My House",
            "Funkytown"
        ],
        "question": "What song did Minnie Riperton have a hit with in 1974?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "one_hit_wonders",
            "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "622a1c3f7cc59eab6f952393",
        "correctAnswer": "Herpetologist",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Entomologist",
            "Barologist",
            "Seismologist"
        ],
        "question": "What is a scientist who studies reptiles and amphibians known as?",
        "tags": [
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62602e994b176d54800e3ce7",
        "correctAnswer": "Belgrade",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Lyon",
            "Geneva",
            "Milan"
        ],
        "question": "Which of these cities is in Serbia?",
        "tags": [
            "cities",
            "europe",
            "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    }
]